<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop"><id>org.kde.plasma-welcome</id><metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license><project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license><name>Welcome Center</name><name xml:lang="ca">Centre de benvinguda</name><name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Centre de benvinguda</name><name xml:lang="en-GB">Welcome Centre</name><name xml:lang="es">Centro de bienvenida</name><name xml:lang="fr">Welcome Center</name><name xml:lang="nl">Welkomcentrum</name><name xml:lang="tr">Karşılama Merkezi</name><name xml:lang="uk">Вітальний центр</name><name xml:lang="x-test">xxWelcome Centerxx</name><summary>Friendly onboarding wizard for Plasma</summary><summary xml:lang="ca">Assistent d'incorporació amistosa per al Plasma</summary><summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Assistent d'incorporació amistosa per a Plasma</summary><summary xml:lang="en-GB">Friendly on-boarding wizard for Plasma</summary><summary xml:lang="es">Asistente de incorporación amigable para Plasma</summary><summary xml:lang="fr">Assistant intégré sympathique pour Plasma</summary><summary xml:lang="nl">Vriendelijke assistent voor Plasma aan boord</summary><summary xml:lang="tr">Plasma için arkadaş canlısı bir ilk kullanım sihirbazı</summary><summary xml:lang="uk">Дружній майстер початкового налаштовування для Плазми</summary><summary xml:lang="x-test">xxFriendly onboarding wizard for Plasmaxx</summary><description><p>Welcome Center is the perfect introduction to KDE Plasma! It can help you learn how to connect to the internet, install apps, customize the system, and more!</p><p xml:lang="ca">El centre de benvinguda és la introducció perfecta al Plasma de KDE! Pot ajudar-vos a aprendre com connectar-vos a Internet, instal·lar aplicacions, personalitzar el sistema, i més!</p><p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El centre de benvinguda és la introducció perfecta a Plasma de KDE! Pot ajudar-vos a aprendre com connectar-vos a Internet, instal·lar aplicacions, personalitzar el sistema, i més!</p><p xml:lang="en-GB">Welcome Centre is the perfect introduction to KDE Plasma! It can help you learn how to connect to the internet, install apps, customise the system, and more!</p><p xml:lang="es">El centro de bienvenida es la introducción perfecta a KDE Plasma. Le puede ayudar a aprender a conectarse a Internet, instalar aplicaciones, personalizar el sistema, y mucho más.</p><p xml:lang="fr">Welcome Center est l'introduction parfaite à KDE Plasma ! Il peut vous aider à apprendre comment vous connecter à Internet, installer des applications, personnaliser le système, et plus encore !</p><p xml:lang="nl">Welkomcentrum is de perfecte introductie in KDE Plasma! Het kan u helpen te leren hoe u een verbinding maakt met het internet, toepassingen installeert, het systeem aanpast en meer!</p><p xml:lang="tr">Karşılama Merkezi, KDE Plasma için en iyi tanıtımı alabileceğiniz biricik yazılımdır. Size; internete bağlanmayı, uygulamalar kurmayı, sistemi özelleştirmeyi ve çok daha fazlasını gösterir!</p><p xml:lang="uk">Вітальний центр є чудовим вступом до Плазми KDE! Він може допомогти вам дізнатися про те, як встановити з'єднання з інтернетом, встановити програми, налаштувати систему тощо!</p><p xml:lang="x-test">xxWelcome Center is the perfect introduction to KDE Plasma! It can help you learn how to connect to the internet, install apps, customize the system, and more!xx</p></description>https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=Welcome%20Center
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/plasma-welcome/plasma-welcome-page-1.png</image>
      <caption>Welcome Center first page: introducing KDE Plasma</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/plasma-welcome/plasma-welcome-page-2.png</image>
      <caption>Welcome Center second page: how to install apps</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/plasma-welcome/plasma-welcome-page-6.png</image>
      <caption>Welcome center sixth page: how to get involved</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots><url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=Welcome%20Center</url><content_rating type="oars-1.0"/><launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.plasma-welcome.desktop</launchable><project_group>KDE</project_group><compulsory_for_desktop>KDE</compulsory_for_desktop></component>
